savevid.com 2014-12-15

# Privacy Policy - Savevid.com

## Privacy Policy

Savevid.com ("Savevid") takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about Savevid's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how Savevid receives, collects and uses information in connection with their website located at Savevid.com and software provided on the Savevid.com website (the website and software collectively referred to herein as "Site").

#### Collection and Use of Information

Savevid does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail, age, gender, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information"). Savevid may request that a user provide an e-mail address if such user wishes to be contacted regarding any offers, updates, newsletters and service related announcements. If a user provides an e-mail address to Savevid, such user authorizes Savevid to send user communications. 

Savevid may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at Savevid's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. Savevid's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information.

Savevid may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. Savevid collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. Savevid will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users.

#### Sharing and Disclosure of Information

Savevid does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. Savevid may disclose your Personal Information if Savevid believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Savevid; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Savevid (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Savevid services or members of the public.

#### Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the Savevid website and software and must LEAVE immediately.

#### Security

Savevid takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although Savevid cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, Savevid has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.

#### Business Transitions

In the event that Savevid goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. Savevid will post a notice on this website of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information Savevid may have prior to such transfer.

#### Changes to Policy

From time to time, Savevid may revise this Policy. Savevid will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information Savevid collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. 

#### Change or Removal of Information

If a user's e-mail address changes, a user may correct such information by sending an e-mail to [support@savevid.com](mailto:support@savevid.com) with the request or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.
